Now, there are two bodies, one moving, one scene.
Which one are you?
Can you be in both?
If you choose one, what happens to the other?
Is either one more you or are both simply appearances?
Look at your right arm.
Please raise your right hand and notice how your body moves.
Please place your right hand on your left shoulder.
Please raise your left hand and notice how your body moves.
Please place your left hand on your right shoulder.
Now place both hands on your lap.
Which one is yours?
Can you be in both?
You don't need to answer.
Just notice that awareness can see two bodies without needing either one to be a fixed self.
Now just observe.